<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Survivalist's Additions (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.SurvivalistsAdditions</packageId>
  <author>mantrasong</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/SurvivalistsAdditions</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>syrchalis.processor.framework</packageId>
      <displayName>[SYR] Processor Framework</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2633514537</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Syrchalis/ProcessorFramework/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>syrchalis.processor.framework</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of cuproPandas mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1207562628
based on the update by mantrasong https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1550854139

- Replaced Universal Fermenter with Processor Framework.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/SurvivalistsAdditions][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Adds new features for primitive and tribal playthroughs.

[h1]Workshop ID:[/h1]
1207562628

[h1]Items Added:[/h1]
[b]Charcoal:[/b] Made in a charcoal pit. Used as fuel for the grill, smoker, and forge.
[b]Grilled Meals: [/b]Come in three varieties: Meat, Veg, and Fine. Provide a small mood bonus, but are slightly more time consuming to make.
[b]Curdled Milk: [/b]Milk that has been curdled with vinegar to make cheese. Made at the brewery.
[b]Cheese: [/b]A processed food made from milk. Has a good flavor and lasts 21 days before rotting.
[b]Smoked Meat:[/b] Like grilled meals, but last for 20 days before rotting.
[b]Smoked Cheese:[/b] Like smoked meat, but made of cheese.
[b]Turnip:[/b] Yields both turnips and turnip greens. Turnips last for a long time, but the greens don't.
[b]Cabbage:[/b] Able to survive and grow in winter temperatures.
[b]Prickly Pear:[/b] Fruit from cacti.
[b]Turnip Salad:[/b] 5 turnip greens can be combined with 5 vegetables to make a salad.
[b]Cabbage Salad:[/b] 5 cabbage can be combined with 5 vegetables to make a salad.
[b]Vinegar:[/b] Fermented berries provide a liquid for preserving vegetables.
[b]Pickled Vegetables:[/b] By combining vinegar with turnips or cabbage, the food can be preserved to last indefinitely.
[b]Shemagh:[/b] A large cloth wrapped around the head which can cover the face when needed. Helps insulate the wearer from the elements.
[b]Jute Fiber:[/b] Used to make burlap fabric.
[b]Burlap:[/b] A scratchy fabric that can be worn at a cost to mood.
[b]Rimshroom:[/b] Rarely spawning mushrooms that are high in protein.

[h1]Objects Added:[/h1]
[b]Grill:[/b] Alternative to the campfire for powerless meal production. Can be used to make 2 meals at a time.
[b]Shelter Door:[/b] Quick to open, but quick to destroy. Can only be made out of wood.
[b]Shelter Wall:[/b] Cheap and quick to build, but quick to destroy.
[b]Shelter Heater:[/b] Cheap wood heater that lasts for a night.
[b]Charcoal Pit:[/b] A pit dug into the ground for burning wood into charcoal.
[b]Smoker:[/b] Stone building that can be used to slowly cook meats and/or cheese, preserving them for a long period of time.
[b]Forge:[/b] Allows crafting metal weapons using charcoal.
[b]Bellows:[/b] Speeds up the crafting speed of the forge and charcoal pit.
[b]Vinegar Barrel:[/b] Allows berries to be fermented into vinegar.
[b]Cheese Barrel:[/b] Allows curdled milk to be made into cheese.
[b]Camp Table:[/b] A lightweight table for making simple things like a shemagh, salads, or pickles.
[b]Camp Butcher Table:[/b] A lightweight table for butchering animals.
[b]Snare:[/b] Used as automated hunting, will catch and kill small animals that wander into it.

[h1]Other Features:[/h1]
[b]Hardy Plants:[/b] Turnips and Cabbage can be grown in colder temperatures than normal plants.



[h1]Save Compatability[/h1]
This mod can be added to existing saves.
Always back up your saves before adding new mods as there is always the possibility for issues.

[h1]Mod Compatability[/h1]
[b]Medieval Times:[/b] Coal is usable in the Forge, Grilled Meals available at the Stone Hearth, other recipes added to Food Prep Station
[b]SeedsPlease:[/b] Seeds added for Turnip, Cabbage, and Jute
[b]Zen Garden:[/b] Saguaro Cactus can be grown in an Orchard Zone to produce Prickly Pear; Cherries, Persimmon, and Crabapple can be used to make Vinegar 
[b]Glowstone:[/b] Forge can be used to weld Glowstones and make Glowstone Tiles.
[b]Cupro's Alloys:[/b] Forge/Crucible can be used to make alloys
No known issues yet, please report any issues

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3052462368][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/SurvivalistsAdditions?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>